octazen.com 2009-05-05

# Octazen Solutions - Contact Importer and Viral Invitation Scripts in Webmails and Social Networks (Hotmail, Yahoo, Gmail, MySpace, Twitter, Hi5, etc)"

At Octazen Solutions ("Octazen"), we respect the privacy needs of our valued customers and members. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the Octazen site and how that information is used.

Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at [info@octazen.com](mailto:info@octazen.com)

### Information Collection and Use

Octazen explicitly asks when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Your personal information is used to create your personal access to our online product, and to contact you in the course of using this product. Financial information that is collected is used to verify, identity and to bill either you or your company for products and services, as applicable. Demographic and profile data collected by Octazen may be used to tailor this web site or any requested email communications, and to display information that is more relevant to you. Octazen also compiles demographic and product use information, but in the aggregate only, and may make that aggregate information publicly available. Under no circumstances will Octazen make any personal information about an individual user available to anyone.

Your email address is used to only send you information that you have requested. As part of your use of our web services, Octazen allows you to elect to receive, or not receive, certain information from Octazen.

Octazen adheres strictly to permission-based email policy. Except as mentioned above, Octazen will not send you unsolicited email information, commercial offers or advertisements. Octazen will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our customer's contact lists (including customer data) to any outside firms nor will Octazen use customer contact lists for our own marketing purposes. All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe. Unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within minutes and no further communications will be sent to users who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information.

### Communications from the Site

**Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new users a welcoming email to verify their new account and confirm their password and username. Established users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Customers can unsubscribe via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email or by sending an unsubscribe request to info@octazen.com. 

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email or by sending an unsubscribe request to info@octazen.com. 

**Service Announcements**

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user's wishes.

### Website Usage Information

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. Octazen does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited. This helps us maintain a superior and informative website for you.

### Security Technology

Octazen has made a substantial investment in the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center. These investments mean that information about the identity and preferences of individual members is never accessible to anyone outside Octazen. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information.

### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when Octazen makes changes to this privacy statement, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

### Contacting Octazen Solutions about Privacy

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us:

**Email**
